<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vilnius Guide</string>

    <string name="img_desc_object_picture">Object picture</string>
    <string name="img_desc_favourites">Favourites</string>
    <string name="img_desc_place_mark">Place mark</string>
    <string name="no_link">No link</string>

    <string name="category_name_arch">Architecture</string>
    <string name="category_name_sculpt">Sculpture</string>
    <string name="category_name_walks">Walks and Sightseeing</string>
    <string name="category_name_cinema">Cinema and Theatre</string>
    <string name="category_name_eat">Eat and Drink</string>
    <string name="category_name_shop">Shopping</string>
    <string name="category_name_favour">Favorites</string>

    <string name="arch_object_name_1">Cathedral basilica</string>
    <string name="arch_place_1">Katedros square 1</string>
    <string name="arch_official_link_1"><![CDATA[Official website: <a href= "http://www.katedra.lt/"
    >www.katedra.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="arch_description_1">The Cathedral of St. Stanislav and St. Vladislav is the most
        important place of worship for Lithuania’s Catholics, and the venue for the country’s main
        Christian and national festivities.\n\nIn 1922, the Cathedral was granted the title of
        \"Basilica\", by Pope Pius XI.\n\nMany key figures in Lithuanian history are buried in the
        Sovereigns’ Mausoleum, which is located beneath the chapel of St. Casimir. Its vaults
        contain the remains of Vytautas The Great, the Grand Duke of Lithuania, and King Alexander
        of Poland. The vaults are not only restricted to kings, either - the two wives of Žygimantas
        Augustas, Queen Elisabeth of Austria and Queen Barbora Radvilaitė. The cathedral containing
        the ashes of King Vladislovas Vaza (Wladyslaw Vasa) are also buried here.\n\nThe cathedral’s
        original temple dates back to between the 13th or 15th century.
    </string>
    <string name="arch_resources_1">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/churches/cathedral-basilica/</string>
    <string name="arch_google_link_1">https://goo.gl/maps/X5pDAfpyeLk</string>

    <string name="arch_object_name_2">Church St. Bartholomew\’s</string>
    <string name="arch_place_2">Užupio str. 17A</string>
    <string name="arch_description_2">Little Saint Bartholomew\’s Church stands on the bank of the
        Vilnia river in Užupis. As you approach it seems to hide, blending in with the houses along
        the street leading to the Bernardine cemetery.\n\n
        The newly-constructed church was the victim of a fire during a war with Muscovy. In 1778 an
        oratory was built by the monks to a design by architect Martynas Knakfusas
        (Martin Knackfuss). This was later converted into a church by Fr Augustinas Stodolnikas in
        1823 - 1824. This church still survives, having had a steeple added in 1881.\n\n
        However it was closed by the Soviet occupation regime in 1949 and converted into a sculpture
        workshop. In 1997 Saint Bartholomew\’s Church was presented to the Belarussian Catholic
        community of Vilnius.
    </string>
    <string name="arch_resources_2">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/churches/st-bartholomew-e2-80-99s-church/</string>
    <string name="arch_google_link_2">https://goo.gl/maps/KkYDSMeDLRD2</string>

    <string name="arch_object_name_3">Church of Bernardine</string>
    <string name="arch_place_3">Maironio str. 10</string>
    <string name="arch_official_link_3"><![CDATA[Official website: <a href= "http://www.bernardinuansamblis.lt">
    www.bernardinuansamblis.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="arch_description_3">A full name of the Church is the Church of St. Francis from
        Assisi (Bernardine). The building is monumental. In case of need it could have been used not
        only for prayer but also for defense. This is testified to by 19 aleois in the northern
        facade. Gothic pointed-arch windows and buttresses stand out on the facade; the 17th-century
        renaissance pediment is adjusted to the Gothic part with a 19th-century fresco. In the times
        of the Soviet occupation the Church was closed down and converted into a warehouse. After
        Lithuania re-established its independence, the Franciscan monks came back to the Church from
        the underground. The Bernardine complex has been declared to be a monument of Lithuanian
        cultural heritage, and in 2008 it was granted the status of a cultural project of importance
        to the state.\n\n2008 Vilnius Bernardine historical-architectural ensemble was reconstructed
        (lofts of the church, choir and administrative premises of the cloister, the gate of the church,
        the passage, the basement and the inner courtyard were renovated), tourist observation paths
        were made.\n\nWell-ordered heritage of Vilnius Bernardine historical-architectural ensemble,
        the entire complex of the tourist route and the Lithuanian museum of sacral art created will
        provide local and foreign tourists with the opportunity to become acquainted with the heritage of
        sacral art and gothic architecture in Lithuania.
    </string>
    <string name="arch_resources_3">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/churches/bernardine-church/</string>
    <string name="arch_google_link_3">https://goo.gl/maps/mmZjjSu4Py32</string>

    <string name="arch_object_name_4">Church of Sts. Johns\'</string>
    <string name="arch_place_4">Šv. Jono str. 12</string>
    <string name="arch_official_link_4"><![CDATA[Official website: <a href= "http://www.jonai.lt">
    www.jonai.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="arch_description_4">One of the picturesque parts of the Vilnius University
        building is the Church of Sts. Johns\' and its bell tower. The full name of the church is
        the Church of St. John the Baptist and St. John the Evangelist.\n\nThe construction of this
        church lasted for almost 40 years and was completed in 1426.
        At that time it was a Gothic building. In 1571 the church was transferred to the Order of
        Jesuits and became a part of the university complexes.\n\nBesides masses, the Church of Sts.
        Johns\' has also witnessed student protests, theatre
        performances, and welcoming ceremonies for kings. In Soviet times, it was turned into a
        warehouse. Later, the University Museum was established here.\n\nToday, the Church of Sts.
        Johns\' performs its main functions once again.
        It was visited by Pope John Paul II in 1993.\n\nThe bell tower of the church, which is 68
        meters high, is among the highest buildings
        in the Old Town. The present facade was designed in the 18th century by the most prominent
        Vilnius Baroque architect, Jonas Kristupas Glaubicas (Johan Christoph Glaubitz).
    </string>
    <string name="arch_resources_4">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/churches/church-of-sts-johns/</string>
    <string name="arch_google_link_4">https://goo.gl/maps/gA7rGGm1Gk62</string>

    <string name="arch_object_name_5">Church of St. Anne</string>
    <string name="arch_place_5">Maironio str. 8</string>
    <string name="arch_official_link_5"><![CDATA[Official website: <a href= "http://www.onosbaznycia.lt">www.onosbaznycia.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="arch_description_5">The church of St. Anne\'s is a masterpiece of the late Gothic
    period. There is no consensus about its originator or its construction period. Popular legend
    says that Napoleon Bonaparte, who was fascinated by the beauty of the church, wanted to take it
    back to Paris in the palm of his hand. Unfortunately, the reality is not that romantic: during
    the march of the Napoleonic army through Lithuania, the church was consigned to the French
    cavalry forces. However, Napoleon did mention in a letter to his wife that \"Vilnius is a very
    beautiful city\".\n\n
    St. Anne\'s Church, which has survived to the present day without changing for over 500 years,
    has become a symbol of Vilnius. At a closer look, one can see the letters A and M in the main
    facade of St. Anne\‘s. The letters A and M could stand for the Latin Ana Mater Maria or Ave
    Maria, i.e. \"Saint Anne - Mother of Mary\" or \"Hail Mary\". Some experts claim that the
    Pillars of Gediminas have been highlighted in the composition of the facade with the three
    towers of the church corresponding to the three pillars.\n\n
    Next to the church there is a bell tower initiating the Gothic style and built in the 19th
    century.
    </string>
    <string name="arch_resources_5">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/churches/church-of-st-anne/</string>
    <string name="arch_google_link_5">https://goo.gl/maps/wLBWPaxUXPq</string>

    <string name="arch_object_name_6">Gates of Dawn</string>
    <string name="arch_place_6">Aušros Vartų str. 12</string>
    <string name="arch_official_link_6"><![CDATA[Official website: <a href= "http://www.ausrosvartai.lt">www.ausrosvartai.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="arch_description_6">The Gates of Dawn is one of the most visited shrines in
        Vilnius that is famous not only in Lithuania but also abroad, worshipped by the
        representatives of other creeds too. This is the only surviving gate of the first original
        five gates in the city wall that was built between 1503 and 1522.\n\nThe gates were first
        mentioned in 1514. At first the Gates of Dawn were called the Medininkai Gate, as it is on
        the road to Medininkai, in Polish Ostra Brama, the “Sharp Gate” because they were in the
        southern end of the city, which was called the Sharp.\n\nLater, due to the cult of the
        Virgin Mary they could be related to the sunrise, dawn.\n\nThe painting of the Blessed
        Virgin Mary, Mother of Mercy, in the Chapel of the Gates of Dawn is known all over the
        world. Many churches in other countries have copies of this painting. The picture, which is
        also called \"Vilnius Madonna\", was painted in 17th century. It is painted in the Renaissance
        style, in tempera on oak boards, later repainted in oil. Since the middle of the 17th
        century it has been said to have miracle-working powers. The Holy Mother of God of the Gates
        of Dawn has been granted the title of Mother of Mercy twice.
    </string>
    <string name="arch_resources_6">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/churches/gates-of-dawn/</string>
    <string name="arch_google_link_6">https://goo.gl/maps/1FKDYBqMhqR2</string>

    <string name="arch_object_name_7">Church of St. Nicholas\'</string>
    <string name="arch_place_7">Didžioji str. 12</string>
    <string name="arch_description_7">Grand Hetman of the Grand Duchy of Lithuania (LDK) Constantine
        Astrozhski built this sanctuary in 1514. In the 18th century the Gothic Orhtodox Church was
        damaged by fire, and thus, restored in the late Baroque style. Later, by order of General
        Governor Muravyov, the Orthodox Church was remodelled in the Russian Byzantine style
        (a marble board in the wall of the chapel is dedicated to Muravyov). Notwithstanding the
        changes, a number of Gothic elements remained in the facade and interior.
    </string>
    <string name="arch_resources_7">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/shrines/russian-orthodox-church-of-st-nicholas/</string>
    <string name="arch_google_link_7">https://goo.gl/maps/4uicWDWd8Mt</string>

    <string name="arch_object_name_8">Palace of the Grand Dukes Of Lithuania</string>
    <string name="arch_place_8">Katedros square 4</string>
    <string name="arch_official_link_8"><![CDATA[Official website:
    <a href= "http://www.valdovurumai.lt/en">www.valdovurumai.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="arch_description_8">The reconstructed Palace of the Grand Dukes of Lithuania, the
        former political, diplomatic, cultural center of the State, was one of the most famous in
        Europe in the 15th-17th centuries and was demolished in the beginning of the 19th century.
        This Palace is excellent located just in the heart of Vilnius, within the confines of Lower
        Castle. Nowadays the Gothic, Renaissance and Early Baroque halls of this multifunctional
        Museum are ideally applicable to organize a different size and content public events,
        official visits, conferences, meetings, seminars, concerts, performances, receptions and
        other.\n\nPart of the reconstructed Palace of the Grand Dukes in Vilnius Lower Castle
        officially transferred to the Museum. In the reconstructed Palace of the Grand Dukes of
        Lithuania there are two exhibition tour routes directly related to the historical functions
        of this residence. The first tour will show the historical and architectural development of
        the palace by highlighting the ancient ruins still in place, excavated artifacts and by
        using models and iconographic materials. The second tour route will bring the visitors into
        the ceremonial halls, which have been reconstructed in such a way as to show the evolution
        of architectural styles - from the late Gothic to the Renaissance to the early Baroque.
    </string>
    <string name="arch_resources_8">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/museums/palace-of-the-grand-dukes-of-lithuania/</string>
    <string name="arch_google_link_8">https://goo.gl/maps/McwNw3iTuUJ2</string>

    <string name="arch_object_name_9">Vilnius Town Hall</string>
    <string name="arch_place_9">Didžioji str. 31</string>
    <string name="arch_official_link_9"><![CDATA[Official website:
    <a href= "https://www.vilniausrotuse.lt/en">www.vilniausrotuse.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="arch_description_9">In 1387, Lithuania became a Christian state and Vilnius was
    granted Magdeburg rights. Thus, there appeared a need for headquarters for the city authorities.
    As the main square of the city was located here, it was decided to build the Town Hall in the
    same place. The building housed the magistrate (in other words, the city councilors) as well as
    court rooms, the treasury, archives, an arms and ammunition warehouse, and rooms for preserving
    standards of measurement. A prison was established in the basement.\n\nThe Town Hall building
    was Gothic to begin with and changed with time. The Town Hall was reconstructed for the last
    time by the architect Laurynas Stuoka-Gucevičius at the end of the 18th century. During that
    reconstruction, the Town Hall turned into a Classical building. In the 19th century, the Town
    Hall was transformed into a city theatre where a famous personality - Polish composer Stanisław
    Moniuszko - conducted the premier of his opera. Among all the Polish composers, only Frederic
    Chopin could be considered more prominent than Moniuszko.\n\nIn the 20th century, an art museum
    was housed in the Town Hall. Today Vilnius Town Hall is a representative building. Many
    different events are organized at the Town Hall during a year: concerts, literary evenings,
    presentations of books, exhibitions and festivals. The pediment of the Town Hall is adorned
    with the coat-of-arms of the city of Vilnius - St Christopher carrying baby Jesus on his
        shoulders.
    </string>
    <string name="arch_resources_9">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/top-20/town-hall/
    </string>
    <string name="arch_google_link_9">https://goo.gl/maps/S7hQp7zuJy42</string>

    <string name="arch_object_name_10">The Bastion of Vilnius City Wall</string>
    <string name="arch_place_10">Bokšto str. 20 / Subačiaus g. 18</string>
    <string name="arch_official_link_10"><![CDATA[Official website: <a href= "http://www.lnm.lt/en/">
    www.lnm.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="arch_description_10">This is part of the Vilnius Defensive Wall, often called
        \"barbican\". The Bastion is a Renaissance-style fortification characterized by its original
        construction. It consists of a tower installed in the city defense wall, underground gun
        ports and a connecting corridor, which turns into a 48-metre long tunnel. The Bastion was
        built in the first half of the 17th century by the German military engineer, Friedrich
        Getkant. The Bastion was severely damaged during the wars with Moscow in the middle of the
        17th century. During World Wars I and II, German military arsenals were located in the
        building. You can enjoy a picturesque view of the Old Town from the Bastion terrace.
    </string>
    <string name="arch_resources_10">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/museums/the-bastion-of-vilnius-city-wall/</string>
    <string name="arch_google_link_10">https://goo.gl/maps/663TMyXx24J2</string>

    <string name="sculpt_object_name_1">Monument to Tsemakh Shabad</string>
    <string name="sculpt_place_1">Mėsinių str. 5</string>
    <string name="sculpt_official_link_1"><![CDATA[Part of <a href= "http://www.mmcentras.lt/projects/70009#vilnius-talking-statues-77966">Vilnius talking statues</a>]]></string>
    <string name="sculpt_description_1">Sculptor: Romualdas Kvintas. 2007\n\nTsemakh Shabad was a
        legendary personality. The doctor was active in various spheres of life, including charity
        (he was one of the heads of the community for supporting refugees), health care (as founder
        of the Ozė health community in Vilnius), education and science as an active figure in the
        Central Jewish Schools Organization and one of the initiators
        of the establishment of YIVO), public affairs (together with J. Vygodskij he re-established
        the Vilnius Jewish Community) and journalism.
    </string>
    <string name="sculpt_resources_1">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/monuments/tsemakh-shabad/</string>
    <string name="sculpt_google_link_1">https://goo.gl/maps/q4ffxj7BJQn</string>

    <string name="sculpt_object_name_2">Monument to Grand Duke Gediminas</string>
    <string name="sculpt_place_2">Katedra square</string>
    <string name="sculpt_official_link_2"><![CDATA[Part of
    <a href= "http://www.mmcentras.lt/projects/70009#vilnius-talking-statues-77966">Vilnius talking statues</a>]]></string>
    <string name="sculpt_description_2">Created by the Lithuanian American Vytautas Kašuba and
        Mindaugas Šnipas. 1996\n\nBesides being the founder of Vilnius and Trakai, Gediminas was
        also one of the most famous rulers of Lithuania. His fame can only be compared to the fame
        of his grandson Vytautas the Great.\n\nGediminas lived between 1275 and 1341 and ruled the
        Grand Duchy of Lithuania for 25 years. He moved the capital of Lithuania from Trakai to
        Vilnius. He was better known as a diplomat who attracted the attention of Europe to
        Lithuania than as a military chief. It was in the letters of Gediminas to Western Europe
        that the name of Vilnius was mentioned for the first time in 1323. This year is considered
        to be the year of the founding of Vilnius.\n\nGediminas succeeded in expanding the state
        borders and the sphere of influence of the Grand Duchy of Lithuania far to the east and
        south. Under the rule of Gediminas, Vitebsk and Volyn were annexed while the lands of Kievan
        Rus fell into a vassal dependence of the Duchy. On their trip west, the army of Gediminas
        even approached Berlin. The area of the Lithuanian state doubled during the times of
        Gediminas.
    </string>
    <string name="sculpt_resources_2">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/monuments/monument-to-grand-duke-gediminas/</string>
    <string name="sculpt_google_link_2">https://goo.gl/maps/vjT34EnYYQ52</string>

    <string name="sculpt_object_name_3">Romain Gary Statue</string>
    <string name="sculpt_place_3">Mindaugo str. / J. Basanavičiaus str.</string>
    <string name="sculpt_official_link_3"><![CDATA[Part of
    <a href= "http://www.mmcentras.lt/projects/70009#vilnius-talking-statues-77966">Vilnius talking statues</a>]]></string>
    <string name="sculpt_description_3">Sculptor: Romualdas Kvintas. 2007\n\nThis small statue was
        made in remembrance of renowned writer Romain Gary, a famous French writer of the 20th
        century as well as a pilot, diplomat and director. The small and frail figure of a boy,
        positioned next to the house where the writer once lived, quaintly stands out against the
        busy crossing. The story of the statue stems from the autobiographic story of the writer
        in his book Promise at Dawn (La promesse de l’aube), in which he tells of his childhood
        in Vilnius and his admiration for a girl named Valentina. Struggling to win her attention
        the writer would cut and eat a gumshoe.
    </string>
    <string name="sculpt_resources_3">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/
        monuments/romain-gary/</string>
    <string name="sculpt_google_link_3">https://goo.gl/maps/RhJjBGkQsk72</string>

    <string name="sculpt_object_name_4">Uzupis Mermaid Sculpture</string>
    <string name="sculpt_place_4">Maironio str. / Užupio str.</string>
    <string name="sculpt_official_link_4"><![CDATA[Part of
    <a href= "http://www.mmcentras.lt/projects/70009#vilnius-talking-statues-77966">Vilnius talking statues</a>]]></string>
    <string name="sculpt_description_4">Sculptor:Romas Vilčiauskas.2002\n\nThe name Užupis means
        \"place beyond the river\". The Vilnia River, often called Vilnelė, is an integral part of
        Užupis. It is therefore quite natural that one of the symbols of Užupis is a bronze mermaid,
        also known as the Užupis Mermaid.\n\nThe mermaid occupies a special niche on the
        embankment of the Vilnia. It is said that it is the mermaid who attracts people from all
        over the world to Užupis. Those who surrender to her charm remain in Užupis forever.
    </string>
    <string name="sculpt_resources_4">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/
        monuments/uzupis-mermaid/</string>
    <string name="sculpt_google_link_4">https://goo.gl/maps/oTe1MNNKntk</string>

    <string name="sculpt_object_name_5">Three Muses Sculpture</string>
    <string name="sculpt_place_5">Gedimino av. 4</string>
    <string name="sculpt_description_5">Sculptor: Stanislovas Kuzma. 1981\n\nThe \"Three Muses\" which
        crown the main entrance to the National Drama Theatre, have already become its symbol. The
        muses of Drama (Calliope), Comedy (Thalia) and Tragedy Melpomene) patronise the wide and
        diverse genres in the theatre\'s repertoire.
    </string>
    <string name="sculpt_resources_5"> http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/monuments/three-muses/</string>
    <string name="sculpt_google_link_5">https://goo.gl/maps/e67ENuGSVQm</string>

    <string name="sculpt_object_name_6">Uzupis Angel Sculpture</string>
    <string name="sculpt_place_6">Užupio str. 9</string>
    <string name="sculpt_official_link_6"><![CDATA[Part of
    <a href= "http://www.mmcentras.lt/projects/70009#vilnius-talking-statues-77966">Vilnius talking statues</a>]]></string>
    <string name="sculpt_description_6">Sculptor: Romas Vilčiauskas. 2002\n\nA sculpture of an angel
    was placed in the central square of Užupis in 2002. The bronze angel, also created by sculptor
    Romas Vilčiauskas, has become the symbol of Užupis.
    </string>
    <string name="sculpt_resources_6">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/monuments/uzupis-angel/</string>
    <string name="sculpt_google_link_6">https://goo.gl/maps/RUZGhB7LCXm</string>

    <string name="sculpt_object_name_7">Monument to Vincas Kudirka</string>
    <string name="sculpt_place_7">Vincas Kudirka square</string>
    <string name="sculpt_official_link_7"><![CDATA[Part of
    <a href= "http://www.mmcentras.lt/projects/70009#vilnius-talking-statues-77966">Vilnius talking statues</a>]]></string>
    <string name="sculpt_description_7">Sculptor: Arūnas Sakalauskas. 2009\n\nA monument to the
        awakener of the Lithuanian nation, writer, publicist, composer, doctor and author of the
        Lithuanian anthem, Dr. Vincas Kudirka has been erected in the square in the centre of the
        capital.\n\nV. Kudirka (1858 - 1899) published most of his works in the magazine of
        literature, politics and science Varpas, which he - along with other kindred spirits - launched
        into publication in 1889. On 15 September 1898, V. Kudirka published Tautiška Giesmė
        (National Song) with notes in the Varpas. This patriotic poem became the national anthem
        of Lithuania in 1919. Following the restoration of independence, Tautiška Giesmė by
        V. Kudirka again became the anthem of Lithuania.
    </string>
    <string name="sculpt_resources_7">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/monuments/monument-to-vincas-kudirka/</string>
    <string name="sculpt_google_link_7">https://goo.gl/maps/1hzetrFqEuN2</string>

    <string name="sculpt_object_name_8">Lamplighter Statue</string>
    <string name="sculpt_place_8">Šv. Jono str.</string>
    <string name="sculpt_official_link_8"><![CDATA[Part of
    <a href= "http://www.mmcentras.lt/projects/70009#vilnius-talking-statues-77966">Vilnius talking statues</a>]]></string>
    <string name="sculpt_description_8">Sculptor: Vytautas Nalivaika. 1986\n\nThis strange statue
        stands near the bell tower of St. John\'s. This sculpture is the work of Vytautas Nalivaika,
        a graduate student of the Institute of Fine Arts (now the Vilnius Academy of Fine Arts).
        It is a sculpture "Lamplighter", which depicts a long-lost representative of the profession
        - a lamplighter.\n\nThe sculpture depicts a man - a lamplighter who builds his hands on the
        heavens, which is built on a high, narrow postage, which reinforces the gracefulness, giving
        the impression of stretching into the top and fits into the Old Town environment. Sculpture
        looks especially mysterious in the evenings when the street lights are on. 2008 an unknown
        street artist painted on a neighboring building a shadow of the statue visible at a certain
        time of the day.
    </string>
    <string name="sculpt_resources_8">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/monuments/lamplighter/</string>
    <string name="sculpt_google_link_8">https://goo.gl/maps/VQWEJ7Rgj342</string>

    <string name="sculpt_object_name_9">Monument to Frank Zappa</string>
    <string name="sculpt_place_9">Kalinausko str. 1</string>
    <string name="sculpt_official_link_9"><![CDATA[Part of
    <a href= "http://www.mmcentras.lt/projects/70009#vilnius-talking-statues-77966">Vilnius talking statues</a>]]></string>
    <string name="sculpt_description_9">Sculptor Konstantinas Bogdanas. 1996\n\nThis monument is
        dedicated to eminent American composer, guitarist and singer Frank Zappa. This performer,
        distinguished for the peculiar style of his creative work, is referred to as the father of
        modern music. Frank Zappa’s music is characterised by its psychedelic style and elements of
        parody, which combine rock, jazz, avant-garde and electronic music.
    </string>
    <string name="sculpt_resources_9">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/monuments/monument-to-frank-zappa/</string>
    <string name="sculpt_google_link_9">https://goo.gl/maps/eKM5Fs67Cvq</string>

    <string name="sculpt_object_name_10">Lithuanian Hounds</string>
    <string name="sculpt_place_10">Barboros Radvilaitės str. 6A</string>
    <string name="sculpt_description_10">Sculptors: Rimantas Keturka, Feliksas Volčakas.
        2015\n\nLithuanian hound is the only Lithuanian hunting dog breed. They track and chase wild
        animals and their melodic barking informs hunters on the location of the prey.
    </string>
    <string name="sculpt_resources_10">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/monuments/lithuanian-hounds/</string>
    <string name="sculpt_google_link_10">https://goo.gl/maps/Hx9cHm2GSFn</string>

    <string name="walks_object_name_1">Pilies Street</string>
    <string name="walks_place_1">Pilies str.</string>
    <string name="walks_description_1">Pilies Street is the oldest and most flamboyant street in the
        Old Town of Vilnius. The street appeared in place of the former road from Vilnius Castle to
        the south, towards Poland and Russia. This was the main road to the castle, with its
        branches finally turning into side streets. The name of Pilies Street was mentioned in
        historical annals as early as 1530.\n\nKings, legates of the Pope, and envoys from other
        countries passed this street on their way to the castle. Noblemen and rich citizens built
        their houses in Pilies Street. Vilnius University occupied a whole quarter of the city
        beside Pilies Street, and university professors used to live there.\n\nThe Botanical Garden
        of Vilnius University was established in one of the courtyards at the end of the 18th
        century. Church processions also went along Pilies Street. The broadest parts of the
        street were occupied by markets: the so-called Great Market near the Town Hall and the
        fish market next to St. Paraskeva\’s Church (Pyatnickaya).\n\nThe street is distinguished
        for its architectural variety: Pilies 12 and 14 are Gothic, Pilies 4 is a Renaissance
        building of an episcopate college; and the pediment of the Church St. John is Baroque.\n\n
        A beautiful view of Gediminas Tower can be seen from Pilies Street.
    </string>
    <string name="walks_resources_1">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/top-20/pilies-street/</string>
    <string name="walks_google_link_1">https://goo.gl/maps/k3JM7krZkaT2</string>

    <string name="walks_object_name_2">Gediminas Avenue</string>
    <string name="walks_place_2">Gediminas av.</string>
    <string name="walks_description_2">Vilnius started developing faster in the middle of the 19th
        century, when the rail line St. Petersburg - Vilnius was built. New industrial, trading and
        residential developments were established next to the Old Town. A new central street of the
        city, Georgij Avenue was built. The names of the avenue changed with the change of
        authorities. Later on the avenue had the names of A. Mickiewicz, Stalin, Lenin, and in 1989
        it was known as Gediminas Avenue. Buildings of the 19th and 20th centuries were built next
        to the avenue, currently housing central government authorities and public institutions,
        trading and catering companies. Gediminas Avenue connects the historical city center,
        Cathedral Square with the Seimas Palace.
    </string>
    <string name="walks_resources_2">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/top-20/gediminas-avenue/</string>
    <string name="walks_google_link_2">https://goo.gl/maps/HRDfNwNbLGA2</string>

    <string name="walks_object_name_3">Literatai Street</string>
    <string name="walks_place_3">Literatų str.</string>
    <string name="walks_official_link_3"><![CDATA[Official website:
    <a href= "http://www.literatugatve.lt/">www.literatugatve.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="walks_description_3">It is thought that this street was named “Literatai” only at
        the second half of 19th century in the honour of Adam Mickiewicz who lived here. The poet
        Adam Mickiewicz lived at the beginning of this street, what is witnessed by three plaques
        on the building in the Lithuanian, Russian and Polish languages.\n\nFrom 2008 a group of
        artists had an idea to revive the street and to decorate it with artworks related with
        litterateurs. A wall was solemnly opened in the street where painters and other field
        artists created plates or small objects made of metal, wood, glass, etc. in the honour
        of litterateurs.\n\nA Modern Art Centre is located on Literatai street (Literatai St. 8),
        http://www.mmcentras.lt.
    </string>
    <string name="walks_resources_3">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/places-of-interest/literatai-street-2/</string>
    <string name="walks_google_link_3">https://goo.gl/maps/dXtVvDP8PeS2</string>

    <string name="walks_object_name_4">Vilnius Cathedral Bell Tower</string>
    <string name="walks_place_4">Šventaragio str. 1</string>
    <string name="walks_official_link_4"><![CDATA[Official website: <a href= "http://www.bpmuziejus.lt">www.bpmuziejus.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="walks_description_4">The Bell Tower, one of the oldest and tallest towers of the
        Old Town, offers a beautiful panorama. Residents and guests of Vilnius will be able to see
        exposition of bells, the old clock of the city, explore the historic pictures of the
        reconstruction of Bell Tower and the Cathedral. Video surveillance cameras installed
        on the top floor of the Bell Tower will help the visitors to get acquainted with the city
        panorama and famous architectural sights. The height of the Bell Tower is 52 m, with the
        cross - 57 meters.\n\nChurch Heritage Museum will organize tours, educational programs and
        events in the Bell Tower. In May - September, the Bell Tower will be open to visitors from
        10 a.m. to 19 p.m. on weekdays and on Saturdays, in cold season - one hour shorter.
    </string>
    <string name="walks_resources_4">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/viewpoints/vilnius-cathedral-bell-tower/</string>
    <string name="walks_google_link_4">https://goo.gl/maps/kmSdksg9Ht32</string>

    <string name="walks_object_name_5">Gediminas\' Tower of the Upper Castle</string>
    <string name="walks_place_5">Arsenalo str. 5</string>
    <string name="walks_official_link_5"><![CDATA[Official website: <a href= "http://www.lnm.lt">
    www.lnm.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="walks_description_5">From 4 November 2017 the access to the territory of The
        Gediminas Hill and Gediminas Castle Tower is temporarily closed due to repair works.\n\nThe
        Vilnius Castle Museum was opened in 1960, and in 1968 it became a subdivision of the
        Lithuanian National Museum. The exposition of the Vilnius Castle Museum displays
        reconstruction models of Vilnius castles of the second part of the 14th and the beginning
        of the 17th centuries, armament, iconographic material of old Vilnius. An observation deck
        on the top of the tower is the best place from which to appreciate a magnificent panorama
        of Vilnius.
    </string>
    <string name="walks_resources_5">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/museums/gediminas-tower-2/</string>
    <string name="walks_google_link_5">https://goo.gl/maps/arz3V1wk4Hs</string>

    <string name="walks_object_name_6">Three Crosses Monument</string>
    <string name="walks_place_6">T. Kosciuškos str.</string>
    <string name="walks_description_6">Sculptor: Antanas Vivulskis. 1916. Kęstutis Šilgalis. 1989
          \n\nSome say, that the origins of the three crosses date back to the 17th century when
          three monks placed them there to pay tribute to a group of fellow monks who were martyred
          in the 14th century. According to the history books, seven monks were killed and seven
          were tied to wooden crosses and floated down the Neris River, with the instruction to
          return to the west where they came from.\n\nThe monument has changed many times, and the
          current one was built by the architect and sculptor, A. Vivulskis in 1989 at the beginning
          of the Rebirth movement. It was built to replace the one that had been removed by the
          Soviet authorities in the 1950s, pieces of which still remain on the far side of the
          slope.\n\nOver the years, the monument has changed many times. The current one was built
          by the architect and sculptor, K. Šilgalis in 1989, when the Soviet Union began to
          collapse.n\nThe Hill of Three Crosses is also known as Kreivasis Hill (the Crooked Hill),
          Plikasis Hill (the Bare Hill) or Tauro Hill.
    </string>
    <string name="walks_resources_6">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/monuments/three-crosses/</string>
    <string name="walks_google_link_6">https://goo.gl/maps/nzmADQpzuQt</string>

    <string name="walks_object_name_7">Bernardine Gardens</string>
    <string name="walks_place_7">Maironio str.</string>
    <string name="walks_official_link_7"><![CDATA[Official website:
    <a href= "http://www.vilniausparkai.lt/parkai/sereikiskiu-parko-bernardinu-sodas/">www.vilniausparkai.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="walks_description_7">Bernardine Garden is situated right in the heart of Vilnius,
        between Gediminas Hill, the Vilnelė River and the Bernardine monastery. After more than a
        year of renovations, the Bernardine Gardens (former Sereikiškės Park) have opened to Vilnius
        residents and guests. The restored park has regained its historic name, which was used from
        the end of the XVth century up until World War II, as well as its authentic appearance,
        which was created by artist Vladislovas Štrausas in the XIX century.\n\nThe park will
        feature botanical and monastic expositions as well as authentic restored park elements,
        such as an alpinarium, a pond, Belvedere Hill, a central square, and paths along the
        Vilnelė River. Fountains have been rebuilt in their historical locations. There will also be
        a rose garden, children’s playgrounds and a musical fountain.\n\nThe botanical exposition,
        which features plants sorted by groups and classes, will be a very special part of the park.
        Visitors will be able to see the ginko tree, the yellow dogwood, Canadian fir, black pine,
        and three of the oldest oak trees in Vilnius. The oldest oak tree in Vilnius, at about 300
        years, can be seen near the entrance on Šv. Brunono Street. There will also be an area for
        students near the botanical exposition, where biology teachers will be able to hold classes
        for their students and children will be able to plant various plants and care for them.\n\n
        The central square features a musical fountain which plays rhythms from popular classical
        and modern pieces.\n\nThe park dates back to 1469, when Lithuanian Grand Duke Kazimieras
        invited the Bernardine monks to Vilnius. They established themselves at the south-eastern
        part of Gediminas Hill and built their monastery and gardens where the park is today. In the
        XVIIIth century, the Vilnius University Botanical Garden was planted, and later, in 1870,
        three separate city gardens - the Botanical, Bernardine and Cathedral gardens - were linked
        into one park accessible to the public.\n\nFree admission. Open daily 7:00 - 22:00.
    </string>
    <string name="walks_resources_7">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/parks-2/bernardine-gardens/</string>
    <string name="walks_google_link_7">https://goo.gl/maps/2J6Kv8g2tRo</string>

    <string name="walks_object_name_8">Vingis Park</string>
    <string name="walks_place_8">M. K. Čiurlionio str. 100</string>
    <string name="walks_official_link_8"><![CDATA[Official website:
    <a href= "http://www.vilniausparkai.lt/parkai/vingio-parkas/">www.vilniausparkai.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="walks_description_8">Vingis Park is situated on a bend of the Neris River and
        covers an area of 160 hectares. In the 15th-16th century, it belonged to the Radvila
        (Radziwill) family, and later it belonged to Bishop Ignas Masalskis. Even later it was owned
        by Vilnius Governor General Leontij Beningsen, who built an elaborate summer house in the
        pine forest. In 1919, after the re-establishment of Vilnius University, a botanical garden
        was located on the grounds of the former manor of Vingis Park. In the 20th century, the
        garden was severely damaged by both a flood and by war. The major part of the recreated
        garden was moved elsewhere.\n\nThe park has two entrances: one from M. K. Čiurlionio Street,
        and the other from Birutės Street. Near the park entrance from M. K. Čiurlionis Street there
        is a Classical chapel and a cemetery for German soldiers. Vingis Park is popular with the
        residents of Vilnius as a place for walking, cycling or roller-skating. Various concerts
        and events are held on the stage erected in the centre of the park. In 1988, Sąjūdis
        meetings were held in the stadium next to the stage, and in 1993 Pope John Paul II
        celebrated a Mass there.
    </string>
    <string name="walks_resources_8">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/parks-2/vingis-park/</string>
    <string name="walks_google_link_8">https://goo.gl/maps/GREMTPnWFa52</string>

    <string name="walks_object_name_9">Pavilniai Regional Park</string>
    <string name="walks_place_9">Belmonto str. 17</string>
    <string name="walks_official_link_9"><![CDATA[Official website:
    <a href= "http://www.pavilniai-verkiai.lt/">www.pavilniai-verkiai.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="walks_description_9">The core of the Pavilniai Regional Park is the valley of the
        Vilnia River. Visitors can follow the tourist route of the park, which goes along the
        Vilnia River from Pūčkorių Dam. The Pūčkorių exposure is a unique geological monument.\n\n
        Nearby you can also visit the territory of the former water mill where a restaurant and an
        entertainment centre Belmontas are situated now. There are also Belmontas waterfalls and
        Belmontas Adventure Park for those who like an active rest. Next to Pūčkoriai exposure,
        on the bank of the Vilnia River, there stands a sun clock. The Administration of the Park
        invites people to take part in cognitive walking tours that are organised in spring and
        autumn.\n\nWhile in Pavilnių Regional Park, take the opportunity to visit Ribiškių hilly
        area. A spectacular view opens from Liepkalnis hill situated alongside Minsk motorway.
        In winter Liepkalnis Hill is the most favourite place of skiers.
    </string>
    <string name="walks_resources_9">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/parks-2/pavilniai-regional-park/</string>
    <string name="walks_google_link_9">https://goo.gl/maps/SiM1TnZfASD2</string>

    <string name="walks_object_name_10">Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="walks_place_10">Kairėnų str. 43</string>
    <string name="walks_official_link_10"><![CDATA[Official website:
    <a href= " http://www.botanikos-sodas.vu.lt">www.botanikos-sodas.vu.lt</a>]]></string>
    <string name="walks_description_10">The Botanical Garden of Vilnius University is not only the
        largest garden in Lithuania (total area is 199 ha) but also the richest one in its
        collections: plants of 9 000 names belonging to 886 genera can be found there, and the best
        and most impressive collections are those of rhododendrons, lilacs, lianas, peonies, dahlias
        and bulb flowers. The Botanical Garden is interesting as an object of heritage - a part of
        an outbuilding of an old estate that has survived in Kairėnai, as well as the old park with
        ponds, has been adapted to being visited. Various cultural events (concerts, art
        exhibitions) are held in the Garden. One can ride on horseback or go for a ride in a
        carriage.
    </string>
    <string name="walks_resources_10">http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/en/what-to-see/places-to-visit/parks-2/botanical-garden/</string>
    <string name="walks_google_link_10">https://goo.gl/maps/6cwg17nPbcA2</string>

    <string name="cinema_object_name_1">Lithuanian National Opera And Ballet Theatre</string>
    <string name="cinema_place_1">Vienuolio av. 1</string>
    <string name="cinema_official_link_1">\+370 5 262 0727</string>
    <string name="cinema_description_1">Vienuolio av. 1\n\ninfo@opera.lt\n\n
        I-V 10:00 - 19:00\n\nVI 10:00 - 18:30\n\nVII 10:00 - 15:00</string>
    <string name="cinema_resources_1">http://www.opera.lt</string>
    <string name="cinema_google_link_1">https://goo.gl/maps/Nfq4cLJueLR2</string>

    <string name="cinema_object_name_2">Lithuanian National Drama Theatre</string>
    <string name="cinema_place_2">Gedimino av. 4</string>
    <string name="cinema_official_link_2">\+370 6 187 5780</string>
    <string name="cinema_description_2">Gedimino av. 4\n\ninfo@teatras.lt\n\n
        I-V 10:00 - 19:00\n\nVI-VII 11:00 - 19:00</string>
    <string name="cinema_resources_2">http://www.teatras.lt</string>
    <string name="cinema_google_link_2">https://goo.gl/maps/vPpSWq3S6N42</string>

    <string name="cinema_object_name_3">Arts Printing House (Menų Spaustuvė)</string>
    <string name="cinema_place_3">Šiltadaržio str. 6</string>
    <string name="cinema_official_link_3">\+370 5 204 0832</string>
    <string name="cinema_description_3">Šiltadaržio str. 6\n\ninfo@menuspaustuve.lt\n\n
        I closed\n\nII-VII 9:00 - 12:00, 13:00 - 22:00</string>
    <string name="cinema_resources_3">http://www.menuspaustuve.lt</string>
    <string name="cinema_google_link_3">https://goo.gl/maps/rxaXCJr44iQ2</string>

    <string name="cinema_object_name_4">Youth Theatre</string>
    <string name="cinema_place_4">Arklių str. 5</string>
    <string name="cinema_official_link_4">\+370 5 261 6126</string>
    <string name="cinema_description_4">Arklių str. 5\n\ninfo@jaunimoteatras.lt\n\n
        I closed\n\nII-VII 11:00 - 14:00, 14:30 - 18:00</string>
    <string name="cinema_resources_4">http://www.jaunimoteatras.lt</string>
    <string name="cinema_google_link_4">https://goo.gl/maps/PUk13azTC6A2</string>

    <string name="cinema_object_name_5">Domino Theatre</string>
    <string name="cinema_place_5">Savanorių av. 7</string>
    <string name="cinema_official_link_5">\+370 656 86383</string>
    <string name="cinema_description_5">Savanorių av. 7\n\ninfo@dominoteatras.lt
        \n\n I-VII 11:00 - 14:00, 15:00 - 19:00</string>
    <string name="cinema_resources_5">http://www.dominoteatras.lt</string>
    <string name="cinema_google_link_5">https://goo.gl/maps/aCAHbim4Z9F2</string>

    <string name="cinema_object_name_6">The Odd Man Theatre (Keistuolių Teatras)</string>
    <string name="cinema_place_6">Laisvės av. 60</string>
    <string name="cinema_official_link_6">\+370 5 242 4585</string>
    <string name="cinema_description_6">Laisvės av. 60\n\nkeistuoliai@keistuoliai.lt\n\n
        I-V 11:00 - 19:00</string>
    <string name="cinema_resources_6">http://www.keistuoliai.lt</string>
    <string name="cinema_google_link_6">https://goo.gl/maps/594U9ohL6ZJ2</string>

    <string name="cinema_object_name_7">Multikino</string>
    <string name="cinema_place_7">Ozo str. 18</string>
    <string name="cinema_official_link_7">\+370 5 219 5378</string>
    <string name="cinema_description_7">Ozo str. 18\n\nvilniusozas@multikino.lt\n\n
        I-VII 10:00 - 22:00</string>
    <string name="cinema_resources_7">http://www.multikino.lt</string>
    <string name="cinema_google_link_7">https://goo.gl/maps/vV64Px6W1uA2</string>

    <string name="cinema_object_name_8">Forum Cinemas Vingis</string>
    <string name="cinema_place_8">Savanorių av. 7</string>
    <string name="cinema_official_link_8">1567 (0,55€/min)</string>
    <string name="cinema_description_8">Savanorių av. 7\n\nI-VII 10:30 - 22:00
    </string>
    <string name="cinema_resources_8">http://www.forumcinemas.lt/</string>
    <string name="cinema_google_link_8">https://goo.gl/maps/T1sK2Cr1jYJ2</string>

    <string name="cinema_object_name_9">Pasaka</string>
    <string name="cinema_place_9">Šv. Ignoto str. 4 / 3</string>
    <string name="cinema_official_link_9">\+370 5 261 1516</string>
    <string name="cinema_description_9">Šv. Ignoto str. 4 / 3\n\nkasa@kinopasaka.lt
    </string>
    <string name="cinema_resources_9">http://www.kinopasaka.lt</string>
    <string name="cinema_google_link_9">https://goo.gl/maps/8HtMatBsLEq</string>

    <string name="cinema_object_name_10">Skalvija</string>
    <string name="cinema_place_10">Goštauto str. 2/15</string>
    <string name="cinema_official_link_10">\+370 5 261 0505</string>
    <string name="cinema_description_10">Goštauto str. 2/15\n\ninfo@skalvija.lt\n\n
        I-V 16:00 - till last session end\n\nVI-VII 13:00 - till last session end</string>
    <string name="cinema_resources_10">http://www.skalvija.lt</string>
    <string name="cinema_google_link_10">https://goo.gl/maps/AA3kKCa8mjq</string>

    <string name="eat_object_name_1">Boom Burgers</string>
    <string name="eat_place_1">Gedimino av. 1</string>
    <string name="eat_official_link_1">\+370 652 14534</string>
    <string name="eat_description_1">Gedimino av. 1\n\nboom@boomburgers.lt\n\n
        I-IV 11:30 - 22:00\n\nV 11:30 - 23:00\n\nVI 12:00 - 23:00\n\nVII 12:00 - 22:00</string>
    <string name="eat_resources_1">https://www.facebook.com/boomburgerslithuania</string>
    <string name="eat_google_link_1">https://goo.gl/maps/tyc3CZaRjdm</string>

    <string name="eat_object_name_2">Briusly</string>
    <string name="eat_place_2">Islandijos str. 4</string>
    <string name="eat_official_link_2">\+370 691 41205</string>
    <string name="eat_description_2">Islandijos str. 4\n\ninfo@briusly.lt\n\n
        I-IV 11:00 - 00:00\n\nV 11:00 - 05:00\n\nVI 12:00 - 05:00\n\nVII 12:00 - 00:00</string>
    <string name="eat_resources_2">http://www.briusly.lt</string>
    <string name="eat_google_link_2">https://goo.gl/maps/bjPwSuMDuXB2</string>

    <string name="eat_object_name_3">Keule Ruke</string>
    <string name="eat_place_3">Pylimo str. 66</string>
    <string name="eat_official_link_3">\+370 623 29839</string>
    <string name="eat_description_3">Pylimo str. 66\n\nnomnom@keuleruke.lt\n\n
        I-V 11:30 - 20:00\n\n
        VI-VII 12:00 - 20:00\n\nV-VI 22:00 - 4:00</string>
    <string name="eat_resources_3">https://www.facebook.com/keule.ruke/</string>
    <string name="eat_google_link_3">https://goo.gl/maps/Snbo6YJ6PKr</string>

    <string name="eat_object_name_4">Maghrib</string>
    <string name="eat_place_4">Užupio str. 22</string>
    <string name="eat_official_link_4">\+370 614 98283</string>
    <string name="eat_description_4">Užupio str. 22\n\ninfo@maghrib.lt\n\nI closed
        \n\nII-IV 16:30 - 22:00\n\nV-VII 12:00 - 23:00</string>
    <string name="eat_resources_4">https://www.facebook.com/MaghribLT/</string>
    <string name="eat_google_link_4">https://goo.gl/maps/Bsmvzz2ppsQ2</string>

    <string name="eat_object_name_5">Gusto Blynine</string>
    <string name="eat_place_5">Aušros Vartų str. 6</string>
    <string name="eat_official_link_5">\+370 647 17777</string>
    <string name="eat_description_5">Aušros Vartų str. 6\n\ngusto@gusto.lt\n\n
        I-VII 9:00 - 22:00</string>
    <string name="eat_resources_5">http://www.gusto.lt</string>
    <string name="eat_google_link_5">https://goo.gl/maps/s1rSEYwxsqz</string>

    <string name="eat_object_name_6">La Boheme</string>
    <string name="eat_place_6">Šv. Ignoto str. 4/3</string>
    <string name="eat_official_link_6">\+370 657 56270</string>
    <string name="eat_description_6">Šv. Ignoto str. 4/3\n\nI-III 11:00 - 24:00\n\n
        IV 11:00 - 01:00\n\nV 11:00 - 02:00\n\nVI 12:00 - 02:00\n\nVII 12:00 - 00:00</string>
    <string name="eat_resources_6">https://www.facebook.com/la.boheme2008</string>
    <string name="eat_google_link_6">https://goo.gl/maps/7FkMJWhaiQv</string>

    <string name="eat_object_name_7">Rene</string>
    <string name="eat_place_7">M. Antokolskio str. 13</string>
    <string name="eat_official_link_7">\+370 5 2126858</string>
    <string name="eat_description_7">M. Antokolskio str. 13\n\n
        vilnius@restoranasrene.lt\n\nI-IV 11:00 - 23:00\n\nV 11:00 - 24:00\n\nVI 12:00 - 24:00\n\n
        VII 12:00 - 21:00</string>
    <string name="eat_resources_7">http://www.restoranasrene.lt</string>
    <string name="eat_google_link_7">https://goo.gl/maps/wLJdmehJnp72</string>

    <string name="eat_object_name_8">Jurgis ir Drakonas (Pylimo)</string>
    <string name="eat_place_8">Pylimo str. 22 D</string>
    <string name="eat_official_link_8">\+370 600 77977</string>
    <string name="eat_description_8">Pylimo str. 22 D\n\nI-V 11:00 - 22:00\n\n
        VI-VII 12:00 - 22:00</string>
    <string name="eat_resources_8">https://jurgisirdrakonas.lt/en/</string>
    <string name="eat_google_link_8">https://goo.gl/maps/Bmg82rYrPpu</string>

    <string name="eat_object_name_9">Uzupio Picerija</string>
    <string name="eat_place_9">Paupio str. 3</string>
    <string name="eat_official_link_9">\+370 5 215 3666</string>
    <string name="eat_description_9">Paupio str. 3\n\nI-V 8:00 - 23:00\n\nVI-VII 9:00 - 23:00</string>
    <string name="eat_resources_9">https://www.facebook.com/UzupioPicerijaPaupio3/</string>
    <string name="eat_google_link_9">https://goo.gl/maps/EN6tKjCuPsu</string>

    <string name="eat_object_name_10">Town</string>
    <string name="eat_place_10">Gedimino av. 26</string>
    <string name="eat_official_link_10">\+370 5 2031228</string>
    <string name="eat_description_10">Gedimino av. 26\n\ninfo@town.lt\n\nBreakfast
        \n\nVI 10:30 - 13:30\n\nVII 10:30 - 15:00\n\nMain menu\n\nI-IV 11:30 - 22:30\n\nV
        11:30 - 23:30\n\nVI 14:00 - 23:30</string>
    <string name="eat_resources_10">http://town.lt/en/</string>
    <string name="eat_google_link_10">https://goo.gl/maps/PgZ2R5hpHss</string>

    <string name="shop_object_name_1">Shopping and entertainment center OZAS</string>
    <string name="shop_place_1">Ozo str. 18</string>
    <string name="shop_official_link_1">\+370 5 210 0151</string>
    <string name="shop_description_1">infocentras@ozas.lt\n\nSHOPS\n\n
        I-VI 10:00 - 22:00\n\nVII 10:00 - 21:00\n\nRESTORANTS\n\nI-VII 10:00 - 22:00\n\nMAXIMA XXX\n\n
        I-VII 8:00 - 22:00\n\nMULTIKINO cinema\n\nI-VII 10:00 - 22:00\n\nX PLANET\n\nI-V 12:00 - 22:00
        \n\nVI 10:00 - 22:00\n\nVII 10:00 - 21:00\n\nPARKING\n\nI-VII 8:00 - 23:30\n\nTo leave parking is
        possible till 1:30.
    </string>
    <string name="shop_resources_1">http://www.ozas.lt/en/</string>
    <string name="shop_google_link_1">https://goo.gl/maps/7uT78Wh5QCp</string>

    <string name="shop_object_name_2">Vilnius AKROPOLIS Shopping Center</string>
    <string name="shop_place_2">Ozo str. 25</string>
    <string name="shop_official_link_2">1588</string>
    <string name="shop_description_2">STORES\n\n
        I-VII 10:00 - 22:00\n\nEUROVAISTINĖ\n\nI-VII 08:00 - 23:00\n\nHYPER MAXIMA XXX\n\n
        I-VII 08:00 - 23:00\n\nERMITAŽAS\n\nI-VI 07:30 - 22:00\n\nVII 08:00 - 22:00
    </string>
    <string name="shop_resources_2">http://akropolis.lt/en/vilnius</string>
    <string name="shop_google_link_2">https://goo.gl/maps/rpitb1ABTU72</string>

    <string name="shop_object_name_3">Shopping and leisure center PANORAMA</string>
    <string name="shop_place_3">Saltoniškių str. 9</string>
    <string name="shop_official_link_3">\+370 5 219 5811</string>
    <string name="shop_description_3">SHOPS\n\n I-VI 10:00 - 22:00\n\nVII 10:00 - 21:00
        \n\nSERVICES\n\nI-VII 10:00 - 22:00\n\n
        RESTAURANTS\n\nI-VII 8:00 - 23:00\n\nRIMI\n\n8:00 - 23:00</string>
    <string name="shop_resources_3">https://www.panorama.lt/en/</string>
    <string name="shop_google_link_3">https://goo.gl/maps/2Z1pWwgqZov</string>

    <string name="shop_object_name_4">City Style Center EUROPA</string>
    <string name="shop_place_4">Konstitucijos av. 7A</string>
    <string name="shop_official_link_4">\+370 616 95680</string>
    <string name="shop_description_4">info@pceuropa.lt\n\n
        PC EUROPA\n\nI-VII 07:00 - 24:00\n\nMOST SHOPS\n\nI-VI 10:00 - 21:00\n\nVII 10:00 - 20:00
        \n\nEUROPA is a centre of style, elegance and fashion. Its concept is based on \"GOOD STYLE,
        GOOD ATTITUDE\" phylosophy, which becomes a foundation for EUROPA brand. It connects style
        with personality, quality concepts with intellect and understanding, conceptual retail
        design with sincere service and beautiful communication. We aim to connect shopping centre
        with personalities, people who strive to succeed in what they do, who seek classic values
        with a twist of modernity.</string>
    <string name="shop_resources_4">http://pceuropa.lt/en/</string>
    <string name="shop_google_link_4">https://goo.gl/maps/ZeLb9hWJjQy</string>

    <string name="shop_object_name_5">OGMIOS CITY Shopping Place</string>
    <string name="shop_place_5">Verkių str. 29</string>
    <string name="shop_official_link_5">\+370 6 800 29292</string>
    <string name="shop_description_5">centras@ogmios.lt\n\n\
        "Ogmios miestas\" is a shopping island in a very convenient place in Vilnius. The shopping
        mall located on the edge of Žirmūnai is easily accessible by private and public transport.
        \n\nIt's like a city in the city, bringing together over 150 famous brands and well-known
        trading companies. Throughout many years of activity, this place has gained its face,
        identity and gained its original surroundings. The territory of 20 hectares in the center
        of the capital has gradually become a coherent whole - the largest trade zone in Lithuania
        for everyone.</string>
    <string name="shop_resources_5">https://www.ogmiosmiestas.lt/</string>
    <string name="shop_google_link_5">https://goo.gl/maps/KBpedCaKpQM2</string>

    <string name="shop_object_name_6">Shopping Center GO9</string>
    <string name="shop_place_6">Gedimino av. 9</string>
    <string name="shop_official_link_6">+370 6559 2550</string>
    <string name="shop_description_6">info@go9.lt\n\nWORKING HOURS
        \n\nI-V 7:00 - 22:00\n\nVI-VII 8:00 - 22:00\n\nRIMI\n\nI-V 7:00 - 22:00\n\n
        VI-VII 9:00 - 22:00</string>
    <string name="shop_resources_6">http://go9.lt/en/</string>
    <string name="shop_google_link_6">https://goo.gl/maps/EZ5Yvr9RwfH2</string>

    <string name="shop_object_name_7">VCUP Shopping Mall</string>
    <string name="shop_place_7">Upės str. 9</string>
    <string name="shop_official_link_7">\+370 5 273 1515</string>
    <string name="shop_description_7">info@vcup.lt\n\nMAXIMA\n\n
        I-VII 8:00 - 22:00\n\nSHOPS\n\nI-VII 10:00 - 22:00\n\nRESTAURANTS\n\nI-VII 10:00 - 24:00\n\n
        Here are nearly 180 sales outlets and 50 service points in the shopping center.\n\nThis part
        of the city promises pleasant memories, where in the commercial space of 26 000 sqm visitors
        feel comfortable thanks to convenient and special layout design of the shopping center.
        Searching for shopping, you can relax in cafes and restaurants, facing the old city of
        Vilnius.
    </string>
    <string name="shop_resources_7">http://www.vcup.lt/en/</string>
    <string name="shop_google_link_7">https://goo.gl/maps/YJzKCi26WQM2</string>

    <string name="shop_object_name_8">Shopping Center BIG VILNIUS</string>
    <string name="shop_place_8">Ukmergės str. 369</string>
    <string name="shop_official_link_8">\+370 5 264 3324</string>
    <string name="shop_description_8">infobig@newsec.lt
        \n\nWORKING HOURS\n\nI-VI 10:00 - 21:00\n\nVII 10:00 - 20:00</string>
    <string name="shop_resources_8">http://www.big-vilnius.lt/</string>
    <string name="shop_google_link_8">https://goo.gl/maps/obzx5vHc2yt</string>

    <string name="shop_object_name_9">Shopping Center MADA</string>
    <string name="shop_place_9">Viršuliškių str. 40</string>
    <string name="shop_official_link_9">\+370 5 241 6583</string>
    <string name="shop_description_9">limada@mada.lt\n\nMADA - is an entire family focused shopping
        center. Modern, however, still retaining its
        cozy environment, MADA is a place where a customer can shop conveniently and quickly. We
        offer a range of stores, which you will not find anywhere else.\n\nEach day shopping center
        MADA is visited by around 14 000 Vilnius residents as well as city guests. MADA shopping
        center arranged in an area of 27 800 square meters hosts over 100 modern shops: grocery,
        clothes, fabric and sewing accessories, footwear, haberdashery, accessories and jewelry,
        cosmetics and perfumery, optician, pharmacy, bank and other companies providing a wide
        range of services.
    </string>
    <string name="shop_resources_9">http://www.mada.lt/en</string>
    <string name="shop_google_link_9">https://goo.gl/maps/uyapVJnjaAt</string>

    <string name="shop_object_name_10">HALES Market</string>
    <string name="shop_place_10">Pylimo str. 58</string>
    <string name="shop_official_link_10">\+370 5 2625536</string>
    <string name="shop_description_10">hale@tugva.lt\n\nII-VI 7.00 -
        18.00\n\nHales market is one of the largest and oldest markets in Vilnius. It was
        constructed in 1906 by a famous architect and engineer Vaclovas Michnevicius.\n\nLocated in
        the Old town, the Marketplace has always been popular among the townspeople and its guests
        for its locally grown and very fresh produce as well as for the home manufactured goods.
    </string>
    <string name="shop_resources_10">http://www.halesturgaviete.lt/en/</string>
    <string name="shop_google_link_10">https://goo.gl/maps/NWP1M9iJmkr</string>

    <string name="favour_object_name_1">Favourites</string>
    <string name="button_share">Share</string>
    <string name="button_more">More</string>

    <string name="top_3_places">Top 3 places</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="about_application">About application</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_application">AboutApplicationActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about_app_description">Application created by Greta Grigutė as part of
        Google developer Android Basics Nanodegree, 5th project. \n\n<b>Pictures authors:</b>
        \n\nLiteratu Street, Cathedral Bell Tower, St. Annes Church, Gediminas av., Bernardine Church - Marius Grigutis;
        \n\nVingis Park, Bernardine Gardens and Grand Duke Gediminas Monument - Rūta Klimienė;
        \n\nAll other pictures - Greta Grigutė.
        \n\n<b>Objects description source:</b> http://www.vilnius-tourism.lt/
        \n\n<b>Icons:</b> https://material.io/icons/
        \n\n<b>Custom ripple effect solution:</b>
        \nhttps://stackoverflow.com/questions/30931889/adding-ripple-effect-to-recyclerview-item/30933094#30933094
        \nand to be able to apply it on card view: https://stackoverflow.com/a/28041873/5770629
        \n\n<b>Coordinator layout learning sources:</b>
        \nhttps://developer.android.com/reference/android/support/design/widget/CoordinatorLayout.html
        \nhttp://saulmm.github.io/mastering-coordinator https://lab.getbase.com/introduction-to-coordinator-layout-on-android/
        \n\n<b>Solution how to add view pager in nested scroll view:</b>
        \nhttps://stackoverflow.com/questions/30580954/viewpager-in-a-nestedscrollview/33385207#33385207
        \n\n<b>Solution to data storage as shared preferences:</b>
        \nhttps://developer.android.com/training/data-storage/shared-preferences.html#WriteSharedPreference
        \n\n<b>Recycler view learning sources:</b>
        \nhttp://www.vogella.com/tutorials/AndroidRecyclerView/article.html
        \nhttps://www.androidhive.info/2016/01/android-working-with-recycler-view/\n\n
        </string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="no_favorites">No favorites.
        \n\nPlease, push heart item to select your favorite</string>
    <string name="email">greta.klimaite@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback about \"Vilnius guide\" application</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="selected_as_favorite">Selected as favorite</string>
    <string name="removed_from_favorites">Removed from favorites</string>
    <string name="email_text">Let\'s visit this place</string>
</resources>
